

### CONTACT



A.Karim Mohamed Sadiq



+973 39147147, 39994585



kareemsadiq413@gmail.com



Manama, Kingdom of Bahrain

### **LANGUAGES**

ARABIC Speak & Write ENGLISH Speak & Write PERSIAN Speak & Write

HINDI Basic SPANISH Basic TURKEY Basic

## SKILLS

Skilled in unstructured, situational, and behavioral interviews. Expert in Microsoft office programs; Word, Excel PowerPoint, emails Outlook & Internet Research

### **HOBBIES**









# A.KARIM MOHAMED SADIQ SALES MANAGER

### **PROFILE**

Achieving growth and hitting sales targets by successfully managing the sales team, Designing and implementing a strategic sales plan that expands company's customer base and ensure it's strong presence, Good team player with good communication and interpersonal skills, Possess good research skills and knowledge in reaching any kind of information, Have leadership and people management competence, How to solve the problems in general

# **EDUCATION**

2000 - 2003

Al Jabbirya Secondary School

## **EXPERIENCE**

MAY 2006 - JAN 2007: PIER CARDIN SHOP

Position: Sales Associates

JAN 2008 - AUG 2014 - AZADEA GROUP ZARA BCC & SEEF

Position: Assistant Manager

SEP 2014 - JUN 2016: A.A. BIN HINDI GROUP

Position: Assistant Manager

JUL 2016 - NOV 2017: PARIS GALLERY

Position: Senior Sales executive

**JUL 2017 - PRESENT: AWAL PRINTING PRESS** 

Position: Sales Manager